Jascha Ostholt



Contact

mail: jascha.ostholt@gmail.com

phone: +49 176 476 467 99

linkedIn: Jascha Ostholt

web: jascha.dev

location: Berlin & Remote

About

I am a passionate web dev with 7+ years of experience in tech, product, UX and agile leadership.

I balance pragmatism with attention to detail and writing clean and future proof code.

stack

Nuxt, Vue, Typescript, Tailwind, GSAP, Three.js

*l've also worked with:*Kotlin, Java (Spring), MongoDB, SQL, Docker

languages

German, English

education

2022 Certified Scrum Product Owner

Scrum.org

2019 B.Sc. Applied Computer Science

HTW Berlin

Web Developer & Product Owner

Experience

- built a portfolio page for Austrian video artist Dominik Galleya: dominikgalleya.at/
- created the web presence for a german school: peter-lenne-schule.de/

C4 Berlin

2023 - today

Web Developer (Freelance)

- developing educational and promotional websites with complex scroll animations
- working for museums and a large german real estate company
- these projects aren't yet published but I am happy to show them personally

elvah

2020 - today

Product Owner & Web Developer

- leading a diverse, cross-functional team of 10-12 people for one of germanys fastest growing mobility startups
- working on web account management and mentoring the web developers of my team
- accomplished full rebranding and customer migration from elvah to e.on drive in just three months
- doubled conversion rate by updating website and registration flow
- improved elvah's search engine visibility by over 300% by building a glossary

kreait

2016 - 2020

Software Developer

- took part in the development of a wide range of apps and services, including both backend and frontend
- designed and developed a microservices architecture for a chat bot
- had the opportunity to work with brands like UEFA, Sport1, Melitta and iFolor